<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="warn">Warn</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="xposed_description">An Xposed module that lets apps run in freeform mode</string>
    <string name="mi_freeform_not_support">Mi-Freeform only supports Android 10 and above</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_message">开发者名称：KindBrave\n\n版本生效日期：2022/8/31\n\n隐私政策版本：1\n\n欢迎你使用米窗，米窗非常重视用户的隐私，米窗本体不会收集、存储、上传任何用户信息；但是米窗使用了Bugly，Bugly使用过程中可能会收集用户信息，Bugly隐私政策请见下文中关于Bugly的描述。\n\n请仔细阅读并理解以下内容，如果你不同意米窗的隐私政策或者对米窗的隐私政策有疑问，请不要使用米窗。\n\n1.米窗本体\n为了保证米窗的正常运行，米窗需要申请以下可能涉及隐私的权限：\n\t1)无障碍权限\n\t\t无障碍权限用于侧边栏的展示等功能，主要利用其高保活能力特性，米窗没有使用无障碍权限对系统、用户进行任何监控。\n\t2)通知使用权限\n\t\t通知使用权是可选权限，即你可以根据自己的情况选择授权或者不授权。通知使用权用户接管通知以对通知添加“小窗打开”功能，米窗虽然获取到了通知内容，但是没有对其进行任何分析、存储、上传。\n\n2.Bugly\nBugly是腾讯旗下一个Bug收集的库，米窗使用Bugly仅用于收集Bug。\n其中，Bugly会收集设备的一些信息，包括Andorid版本号、CPU架构等；会使用互联网权限上传崩溃日志。\n更详细的Bugly隐私策略，请阅读《Bugly SDK个人信息保护规则》，网址：https://privacy.qq.com/document/preview/fc748b3d96224fdb825ea79e132c1a56</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">" "</string>
    <string name="service_not_running">Shizuku/Sui service is not running, have you authorized Shizuku/Sui for Mi-Freefrom?</string>
    <string name="overlay_no_permission">No floating window permission</string>
    <string name="app_is_running">The app is already in freeform mode</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="coolapk_my_name">Coolapk follow me</string>
    <string name="add_qq_group">Join the QQ exchange group</string>
    <string name="add_qq_group2">Join the QQ exchange group 2</string>
    <string name="add_qq_channel">Join QQ channel</string>
    <string name="add_telegram">Telegram exchange group</string>
    <string name="open_source">Github</string>
    <string name="try_to_init_shizuku">Trying to activate Shizuku service…</string>
    <string name="try_to_init_xposed">Having Xposed does not help Mi-Freeform to open freeform, but Mi-Freeform can prevent the application from jumping out of the freeform to full screen after having Xposed. To use Xposed, you need to go to the Xposed management application (such as Lsposed) to check the \"system framework\" for the Mi-Freeform and restart the device</string>
    <string name="sui_service_description">You can already experience Mi-Freeform service</string>
    <string name="no_service_description">Neither Xposed nor Sui/Shizuku services start</string>
    <string name="start_market_fail">Failed to open app store</string>
    <string name="start_coolapk_fail">Failed to open Coolapk</string>
    <string name="start_qq_fail">Failed to open QQ</string>
    <string name="sui_start_short">Sui activated</string>
    <string name="shizuku_start_short">Shizuku is active</string>
    <string name="xposed_start_short">Xposed exists</string>
    <string name="accessibility_desc">Mi-Freeform keep alive service. This service can ensure the background survival of Mi-Freeform. Mi-Freeform does not collect any information through this service.</string>
    <string name="request_overlay_permission_fail">Unable to jump to the settings interface, please manually go to the settings to enable the \"display on top of other application interfaces\" permission of the Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="request_overlay_permission">Please select the Mi-Freeform to enable the permission of \"display in the upper layer of other application interface\"</string>
    <string name="reset_success">Reset Successful,Some settings take effect after restarting Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="label_floating_apps">Sidebar shortcut app selection</string>
    <string name="label_notification_apps">Take over notification app selection</string>
    <string name="all_apps">All apps</string>
    <string name="edit_apps">edit</string>
    <string name="xposed_no_start">(Optional) Xposed not activated</string>
    <string name="xposed_start">Xposed exists, please check the system framework and restart</string>
    <string name="permission_info">In order to ensure the normal operation of the software, Mi-Freeform needs to apply for the following permissions. Among them, the Xposed permission can prevent the application in the freeform from jumping out to the full screen; the Shizuku/Sui permission is used to open core functions such as the freeform; the accessibility permission is used to ensure the survival of the Mi-Freeform; the overlay window permission is used to display the freeform interface; notification The usage rights are used to open the freeform of the notification app.</string>
    <string name="shizuku_no_start">Shizuku/Sui</string>
    <string name="sui_start">Sui service is already running</string>
    <string name="shizuku_start">Shizuku service is already running</string>
    <string name="accessibility_no_start">(Optional) Click to apply for accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibility_start">Accessibility services are already running</string>
    <string name="overlay_no_start">Click to apply for overlay window permissions</string>
    <string name="overlay_start">Overlay window is authorized</string>
    <string name="notification_no_start">(Optional) Click Notification Access</string>
    <string name="notification_start">Notify that usage rights have been authorized</string>
    <string name="label_permission">Access Request</string>
    <string name="no_permission">There are also necessary permissions without authorization</string>
    <string name="xposed_permission_intro">To enable the Xposed function, you need to go to the Xposed manager (such as Lsposed), check the system framework and restart. Please note that even if the Xposed function is enabled here, there is still a possibility of injection failure. For details, please refer to the log with the [Mi-Freeform] tag in Xposed.</string>
    <string name="next_step">Next step</string>
    <string name="label_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="category_base">basic settings</string>
    <string name="switch_hide_recent">Hide from recent tasks</string>
    <string name="switch_hide_recent_summary">Hide from multitasking in Mi-Freeform. Cross out the Mi-Freeform and then re-enter to take effect</string>
    <string name="preference_reset_overlay_setting">Reset overlay position and size</string>
    <string name="preference_reset_overlay_setting_summary">Reset the position and size of the recorded freeform and sidebar. It can be used for the problems that the above two run out of the screen and cannot be controlled or the record freeform size not normal</string>
    <string name="compatible_title">Compatibility mode startup freeform (experimental)</string>
    <string name="compatible_summary">Use compatibility mode to start the freeform, this mode can solve the problem of abnormal interface size such as software notification in the freeform and full screen. Compatibility mode widget interface scaling is supported in the next version.</string>
    <string name="category_freeform">freeform settings</string>
    <string name="setting_freeform_dpi_title">Freeform interface scaling - vertical screen</string>
    <string name="setting_freeform_landscape_dpi_title">Freeform interface scaling - horizontal screen</string>
    <string name="change_dpi_title">Modify freeform scaling when screen is rotated (experimental)</string>
    <string name="change_dpi_summary">If this option is not enabled, the scaling ratio of the interface in the freeform set above will only take effect when the freeform is started for the first time. When this option is turned on, when the screen is rotated, it will try to change the zoom ratio to achieve the effect of the above settings, but some applications will refresh the content. More seriously, UI exceptions may occur on some devices</string>
    <string name="use_sui_refuse_to_fullscreen_title">Use Shizuku/Sui to prevent apps from popping out of freeform to full screen (experimental)</string>
    <string name="use_sui_refuse_to_fullscreen_summary">Currently only supports Android 12+. This feature is recommended to be enabled only when there is no Xposed or Xposed blocking fails. Try using Shizuku/Sui to prevent apps inside the freeform from popping out of the freeform to full screen. This function is still under testing, and there is no guarantee that the blocking will be successful, and it will cause problems such as screen flickering, freezing, etc.</string>
    <string name="category_floating">sidebar</string>
    <string name="switch_floating">Global sidebar</string>
    <string name="switch_floating_summary">Open freeform apps via sidebar</string>
    <string name="menu_floating_position">Sidebar position</string>
    <string name="preference_quick_floating_app">Quick application</string>
    <string name="preference_quick_floating_app_summary">Select apps displayed in the sidebar that can quickly launch freeform</string>
    <string name="category_notify">notification</string>
    <string name="switch_notify_freeform">Take over selected app notifications</string>
    <string name="switch_notify_freeform_summary">When the selected app sends a notification, Mi-Freeform will intercept and send a notification with the same content, but the app can be opened through Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="preference_notification_apps_summary">Select the app to take over</string>
    <string name="preference_notification_apps">Take over notification app</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="choose_all">Choose All</string>
    <string name="choose_all_cancel">Deselect All</string>
    <string name="label_sort_apps">Quick app sorting</string>
    <string name="freeform_channel_id">Freeform app notifications</string>
    <string name="open_by_freeform">Open By Freeform</string>
    <string name="require_accessibility">Please grant accessibility permission</string>
    <string name="require_notification">Please authorize notification usage rights</string>
    <string name="choose_freeform_app">Choose a freeform app</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Use Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="guide_a">Through the following tutorials, you will get started with Mi-Freefrom faster</string>
    <string name="button_step_a">1. Preparation before using the Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="guide_a_text">\t\t<font color="red"><b>Special reminder: Mi-Freeform cannot run in Vulkan mode, if you have turned on similar options (such as Kaleidoscope ROM-Settings-System-Lab \"Use Vulkan for HWUI Rendering\"), please turn off this option, forcibly stop the Mi-Freeform and run again, otherwise it will crash! Please note that switching the Vulkan option may cause the device to fail to start. Please do not try on the main device!</b></font>\n\t\tBefore using the meter window, you must be introduced to the use of the meter window. <b>Mi Window requires Xposed and Shizuku/Sui</b>, if you don\'t know the above tools, please check the relevant information by yourself, <b>use Mi-Freeform after installation on the device</b>. \n\t\tMi-Freeform currently supports a variety of startup methods, including: 1. Sidebar, 2. Quick tile 3. Reserved activities, etc. In the future, Mi-Freeform will support more startup methods.</string>
    <string name="button_step_b">2. Understand the control method of Mi-Freeform</string>
    <string name="guide_move">How does the freeform move? How to hang? Drag the indicated button to the four corners of the screen to try it. To resume from the suspended state, just click the freeform interface.</string>
    <string name="guide_back">Very good! So how to return to the previous interface in the freeform? Click on the indicated button</string>
    <string name="guide_close">Awesome! Want to close the freeform? Click on the indicated button</string>
    <string name="guide_to_full">Really not bad! So if the freeform is full-screened? Try pressing and holding the button</string>
    <string name="guide_to_back_stage">Clever! Don\'t want to terminate the freeform program, and don\'t want it to be displayed on the screen? Try to hang in the background and long press the right button to achieve</string>
    <string name="guide_scale">Incredible! Programs suspended in the background will be displayed at the top of the freeform application selection interface, click to resume. The last item, if you zoom the freeform, try dragging the highlighted part of the lower corner of the freeform</string>
    <string name="guide_success">Congratulations, you have understood the basic operation of the Mi-Freeform. Now, you can close the demo window by clicking the close button</string>
    <string name="no_step_done">Please complete all instructions</string>
    <string name="have_done">Done</string>
    <string name="test">1</string>
    <string name="remember_position_title">Remember freeform position and size</string>
    <string name="remember_position_summary">Remember the position and size of freeform when it was last closed</string>
    <string name="senior_info">Thanks. But for the time being, Mi-FreeForm maybe not support donate from outside mainland China:(</string>

    <string name="donation_label">Donation</string>
    <string name="open_alipay_fail">Open Alipay Failed</string>
    <string name="alipay">Alipay</string>
    <string name="pay_list">Donate List</string>
    <string name="so_sad">No! I don`t want to donate</string>
    <string name="wechat">Wechat</string>
    <string name="arrow_down" translatable="false">⬇</string>
    <string name="arrow_left" translatable="false">⬅</string>
    <string name="arrow_right" translatable="false">➡</string>

    <string name="fenshen">User</string>
    <string name="running">(Running)</string>
    <string name="floating_label">Open the Sidebar</string>
    <string name="manual_adjust_freeform_rotation_title">Manually adjust widget orientation (experimental)</string>
    <string name="manual_adjust_freeform_rotation_summary">When turned on, allows to manually rotate the freeform orientation by double-clicking the bottom bar middle button. Due to the diversity of devices, this function may not meet expectations, please treat it rationally</string>
    <string name="foreground_notification_name">ForegroundService Notification</string>
    <string name="foreground_notification_title">Mi-Freeform is running in the background</string>
    <string name="foreground_notification_text">Click to open sidebar</string>
    <string name="service_type_title">Keep alive service type</string>
    <string name="service_type_summary">Accessibility by default. If accessibility is a problem on your device, you can select foreground notifications. When switching to foreground notifications, make sure accessibility is turned off. If accessibility works fine on your device, do not select foreground notifications</string>
    <string name="require_start_accessibility">Please enable accessibility services and try again</string>
    <string name="require_stop_accessibility">Please turn off accessibility services and try again</string>
    <string name="require_foreground">Please make sure the foreground service is running, you can try to switch the keep-alive service type to solve the problem</string>
    <string name="home_accessibility_warn_message">The current keep-alive mode is the accessibility service, so the accessibility service needs to be enabled to run normally. If you have problems with accessibility services on your device or you do not want to use accessibility mode, you can switch to keep-alive mode in settings</string>
    <string name="go_to_start_accessibility">Turn on accessibility</string>
    <string name="go_to_change_service_type">Go to switch keep-alive service type</string>
    <string name="accessibility_no_start_home">Click to apply for accessibility</string>
    <string name="donate_message">Mi-Freeform can be experienced without compulsory payment, but maintaining Mi-Freeform consumes a lot of energy from developers. Donations can make developers more motivated to maintain :)</string>
    <string name="exchange">Communication&amp;Feedback</string>
    <string name="donate_wechat_title">Save the screenshot and scan the code on WeChat:)</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="guide_help">Help</string>
    <string name="guide">Function guide</string>
    <string name="question">Common problem</string>
    <string name="create_display_fail">Failed to create screen, which means Mi-Freeform may not work on this ROM, please contact the developer</string>
    <string name="step_b_warn">Please make sure you have read and fully understood the content in 1. Preparation before using the Mi-Freeform before starting this tutorial</string>
    <string name="to_read_step_a">To read</string>
    <string name="start_step_b">Start the tutorial</string>
    <string name="open_api">Open API</string>
    <string name="preference_start_by_recent_view_summary">How to open Mi-Freeform in multi task interface? After checking the desktop in xposed manager, long press the application icon on the multitasking interface. This function only supports launcher3 desktop</string>
    <string name="preference_start_by_recent_view_title">Start in RecentView</string>
    <string name="input_freeform_dpi">Range: - 500 ~ 500</string>
    <string name="freeform_dpi_dialog_title">Enter scale value</string>
    <string name="to_default">To default</string>
    <string name="recent_label">Running Freeform</string>
    <string name="auto_scale_title">Auto Scale Freeform(Test)</string>
    <string name="auto_scale_summary">Freeform can be zoomed in according to the free ratio</string>
    <string name="floating_alpha_title">Sidebar Transparency</string>
    <string name="recent_open_by_freeform">Open by Mi-Freeform</string>
</resources>